Vyacheslav Ostapkevich

Front-end Developer











ABOUT ME

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming that inspires me everyday. I have experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript in team. Now I improve my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. I spend my leisure time on Codewars or by improving english skills. Open to your suggestions.

SKILLS

- React/Redux
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/REST api/Postman
- TDD/Storybook
- React-hook-form/Formik
- MaterialUI/Ant Design
- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Git

CONTACTS



+375 (29) 667-10-53



slavaost-it@mail.ru



Minsk, Belarus

WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Network (May 2022 - Dec 2022)

Used technologies: React/Redux/TypeScript/Redux-thunk/React-router-dom v6/React-hook-form/Axios/Jest:

Social network app with using react hooks, routing, lazy loading, working with REST api, login/logout flow, pagination, form and validation/file uploading using unit-tests for code workability check. **Github link**

Todolist (Mar 2021 - Sen 2022)

Used technologies:

React/Redux/Redux-Toolkit/React-router-dom v6/
Jest(Unit-Tests) /Storybook/Axios /Formik/Material UI;
Todolist app created with react hooks, routing and
redirects, material UI, REST api request/response flow,
unit-tests and etc. **Github link**

EDUCATION

2022

IT-INCUBATOR, front-end

Front-end developer with teamwork experience in creating applications by using React, Redux, TypeScript, Axios and other technologies

2008 - 2013

Admiral Makarov State University of maritime and inland shipping

Engineer specializing in hydraulic engineering

LANGUAGES

- Russian nativ
- English pre-intermediate (in progress)